It's embarrassing, already.
恥 ず かしいよ、もう
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
I'll like it soon.
このうちにいいね
Oh, really?
え、本当ですか?
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
Because my eyes are swimming.
目が泳いでるから
Embarrassing, embarrassing.
恥ずかしい恥ずかしい
Would you like to say hello to the uncles watching all over the country?
全国の見てるおじさまに挨拶してくんない?
Nice to see you.
おしめまして
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいね
My face is turning red.
顔が赤くなってる
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいね
I have a few words to say.
ちょっと挨拶あるよ
It's close.
近いね
But I think the people watching want to get closer.
でも、見てる人たちはもっと近づいてほしいと思ってるから
so?
そんなに?
I'm looking forward to it.
楽しみだな
I tried to imagine myself naked.
裸想像してみた
on second thoughts.
やっぱり
Is it almost big?
ほぼ大きいのかな?
No, it's that good.
いや、そんなにいいですよ
Is that so?
そう なの?
I'm looking forward to it.
楽しみだな
Who do you like?
好きな人は?
No, but I don't really like romance that much now.
いや、でも、今はそんなに恋愛は好きじゃない
Isn't it quite possible to leave if it's a university?
大学だったら去っては結構あるんじゃないの?
I don't really go, I don't go to the country.
あんまり、私が行かない、国に行かないから
What type of person are you?
どんな人タイプなの?
picture?
え?
kind person?
優しい人?
Okay, okay.
よし、よし
Gentle, gentle.
優しい、優しい
You're kind, aren't you?
優しいでしょ?
A little bit from now...
今からちょっと...
You have to be kind to me too.
優しくしないとね、こっちもね
Oh, please.
あ、お願いします
This is how I feel.
こういう気持ちに
Oh, it's so fluffy.
あ、ふわふわです
This definitely smells like a teenager's teeth.
やっぱり10代の歯匂いだね、これ
picture?
え?
I understand?
わかります?
Things will change when you turn 20.
20歳くれたら変わるからね
There's a lot going on.
いろいろしてくるのあるよ
We haven't talked lately.
最近って会話しないから
Well, not really.
そうですね、あんまり
I feel kind of embarrassed.
なんか、恥ずかしくて
I can't invite you.
誘ったりできない
You don't have to invite it yourself.
自分から誘わなくてもいいじゃん
After all, the man should take the lead.
男の人からリードしてくれ、やっぱり
Eh, are you coming, man?
え、来ますかね、男の人
Isn't it coming?
来るんじゃない?
I'm not used to it.
慣れてなくて
Maybe you're a dull person?
もしかして、鈍い人?
Are you as dull as the other person you see?
相手の際に見るくらい鈍い人?
Is that so?
そうなのかな?
そうなの?
How old is Kitsuji?
きつじさんが誰くらいぶり?
No, what?
いや、え?
I had no idea.
全然知らなかった
that's right.
そうです
More than 1 year.
1年以上
More than 3 years.
3年以上
About a year.
1年ぐらい
It's okay, because.
いいんですよ、だって
Suddenly.
いきなり
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Do you like light blue?
水色好きなの?
I like light blue.
水色好きです
You're calm, okay?
落ち着いてんだね、じゃあ
I'm sweaty.
汗ばんでる
Are you nervous?
緊張してるの?
I am doing.
してます
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいです
It's Gappo.
ガッポですよ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Could you please take this off?
これ脱いでもらおうかな?
By yourself.
自分で
picture?
え?
what are you doing?
何してるの?
Is it easy to feel?
感じやすいの?
I think it's easy to feel.
感じやすいと思います
Is it okay for every house in the country to have a garden?
全国の家にお庭があっていい?
I'll be separated.
離されちゃう
That's right.
そうだよ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
It's been a while since I became a mother of a teenager.
久しぶりに10代のお母さん
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Does it smell?
臭いの?
It stinks.
臭いです
Let me bite?
噛ませる?
Excuse me a little?
ちょっと失礼?
Yeah.
うん
I'm so wet.
めっちゃ濡れてる
It's wet here too
ここも濡れて
Ru.
る
It's embarrassing.
恥 ずかしい
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
It's cleaning up a lot.
大きく洗い出してるね
I'm so wet.
めっちゃ濡れちゃってる
How can I make it into pants?
どうやっちゃパンツにならそうかな?
It stretches.
伸びます
extend?
伸びる?
Is it the same as sleeping on your own?
自分で寝るのと同じ?
It's so embarrassing.
めっちゃ恥ずかしい
I'll get out of the way.
邪魔なしちゃう
Now it looks like a flycatcher.
これでハエグみたいになってるよ
Isn't it good to do this?
こうするとよくない?
It's rolling.
転がってる
What do you look like?
なんていう格好してるの?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Lower your butt a little.
少しお尻を下して
Did a live machine come out?
生のマシンが出てきた?
Messed up.
めちゃめちゃ
70% of the screen is filled with pussy.
画面の7割もママンコでいっぱいになってる
It's strange, I can see insects.
不思議なな、虫が映ってる
went?
行 った?
When I said I was going now, an amazing frequency came out.
今行くって言ったとき、 すごい周波が出てきたね
Has Six Night ever done it?
シックスナイトがしたことある?
Impossible.
無理
Let's try it
やってみよう
mosquito.
か
Amazing walk.
すごい 歩き
Can I watch it with you?
一緒に見てもいい?
Let it all out inside.
中でいっぱい出して
Do you understand?
わかる?
Did it come out?
出てきたの?
Can you please spread the word to someone other than me?
俺以外広げてみてくれない?
That's how I feel.
そんな気分よ
Maybe it's a painful day?
もしかして痛い日?
I might come out.
出ちゃうかも
I've been exposed before, I won't keep my mouth shut.
出されたことある、口抜かない
Don't talk until you're done.
手終わるまで口抜かないでね